

### **Contacts**

Contacts: +380974335970

Email: rudomanovdmitrij@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="www.linkedin.com/">www.linkedin.com/</a>
GIT: <a href="https://github.com/">https://github.com/</a>

#### **Tech Skills**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- scss
- GIT
- JavaScript
- WebPack
- React
- Redux

# **Soft Skills**

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Decision-making
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Stress management

# Language Skills

Russian : NATIVEUkrainian : NATIVE

English : Upper-intermediate

# **Front-End Developer**

# **Dmitrij Rudomanov**

I'm a Frontend developer with experience in building websites and APP's. Whether you're trying to win work, list your services or even create a whole online store – I can help! I'm experienced in HTML and CSS3, SCSS, JS and React. Regular communication is really important to me, so let's keep in touch!

### **Projects**

1.	<u>'PHONEBOOK' web-app</u> [ HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript,React,Redux ]
2.	'FILMOTEKA' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
3.	'WebStudio' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
4.	'ICECREAM' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
5.	'WOODER' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS ]
6.	'OFDR' Insurance web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
7.	'FUNIRO' web-store [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
8.	'LOGO' sport web-store [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
9.	'BENTLEY' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
10.	'BINARY' web-site
11.	'Prime-One' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]
12.	'BIKE' web-site [ HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript ]

# **Work Experience**

# Waiter Restaurant 'SHO PO CHEM'

June 2019 - September 2019 | Country Ukraine

- Taking orders from visitors
- · Customer service

#### Web-site editor Svet-LED Company

September 2019 - January 2019 | Country Ukraine

- Editing the list of products on the site
- · Products information update

### **Education**

## **PSACEA**

# International Economics and business

September 2018 - June 2023 | Country Ukraine

# **Additional Education**

#### GOIT

# FULL STACK course online

August 2021 - June 2022 | Country Ukraine